YASSER SHEHAB

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

1 01092372601

yassershehab9@gmail.com

Cairo, Helwan

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/yas ser-shehab-el-dean-494638182/

https://github.com/Yasser-Shehab

PROFILE

A Front-End Developer with experience in Implementing a perfect pixel design and creating visually appealing websites. also, I have a good understanding of the back-end as I worked with Back-End Technologies, I am a strong team player, but I can also work independently when needed.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-End

Back-End

HTML5 & CSS

Nodejs

REACT

Express

Redux

MongoDB

Javascript RESTFUL APIS

MySQL

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance

Jan 2022- Feb 2022

- Worked on a CRM system for an Engineering Company
- Implemented the Website from a Figma Design to a pixel-perfect design using SCSS
- Worked on Creating APIs and integrating them into the Front-End

FULL STACK DEVELOPER (MERN) INTERNSHIP

ΙT

Nov 2021 - April 2022

 Got a practical study on many topics in Web Development like JavaScript/Typescript concepts and a deep level of understanding of how they internally work. and worked on Back-End technologies like Nodejs and Express.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR DEGREE

Modern Academy 2015-2019

Typescript

LANGUAGES

Arabic - Native

English - Proficient

COMMUNITY MANAGER

Press-X

Aug 2018 - Sept 2019

• Successfully made over 200 competitive tournaments.

COURSES

JAVASCRIPT ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES

FreeCodeCamp

Aug 2022

PROGRAMMING WITH JAVASCRIPT

META

Aug 2022

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROFESSIONAL NANO DEGREE

Udacity

Dec 2020

FUNDAMENTALS OF GRAPHIC DESIGN

Coursera

Sept 2020

PROJECTS

CRM SYSTEM FOR A CONSTRUCTION COMPANY

Live: https://mile-frontend.vercel.app/

MY READS

Live: https://my-reads-topaz.vercel.app/

Code: https://github.com/Yasser-Shehab/MyReads

MOVIE APP

Live: https://movie-app-pi-wine.vercel.app/

Code: https://github.com/Yasser-Shehab/Movie-App

CLOTHING STORE FRONT PAGE

Live: https://clothing-store-sage.vercel.app/

Code: https://github.com/Yasser-Shehab/clothing-store

TO-DO APP

Live: https://to-do-react-three.vercel.app/

Code: https://github.com/Yasser-Shehab/To-Do-React